If you want to meet the person
you mentioned earlier,
the key is in my pocket.
Please don't kill me.
I'm sorry for everything. Please!
Where is Seong Gi-hun?
Room 410!
Police. Hands above your head!
Seong Gi-hun.
You are under arrest
on suspicion of murder.
You have the right to an attorney,
and you have the right to--
Who are you?
Are... Are you Mr. Seong Gi-hun?
I've been helping Mr. Kim
look for the man with the ddakji.
My name is Choi Woo-seok.
We've been sending you pictures
from the subway stations every day!
Don't you remember?
We've never met in person,
but I've heard
a lot about you from my boss.
He said you were a great man
who came to settle your debt voluntarily.
He said he'd never seen anyone like you...
That bastard.
Did you kill him, Mr. Seong?
You goddamn son of a bitch!
That bastard...
That bastard killed the boss.
I played two rocks by mistake.
He had paper and scissors.
All he had to do was pick paper.
But he didn't.
Like a fool...
OCTOBER 31 MIDNIGHT
CLUB HDH
SQUID GAME 2
EPISODE 2
HALLOWEEN PARTY
Excuse me!
Hey!
Wake up!
Open the window.
What are you doing here?
I work here.
I have to be here early tomorrow.
Doesn't mean you can
sleep out here in your car.
I'll get in trouble
if my superiors find out.
I think I've seen you here before.
I'm sorry. I'll move my car tomorrow.
There won't be a next time.
Otherwise, I'll have to report you.
Okay.
Detective Hwang Jun-ho.
Now I remember.
You came to see me
at my house once before.
We've met twice.
Once in front of your house, and again...
on that island.
Do you remember?
The night of the ruckus in the dorm.
The masked men went in to stop it.
Were you one of them?
I snuck in there in disguise
to find my brother.
How can I believe you?
One of the masked men asked you
about someone named Hwang In-ho.
Player 456.
Is there a man named Hwang In-ho here?
We do not know each other's names.
That was me.
Hwang In-ho is my brother.
Who's the man you killed?
He's a recruiter
who finds players for the game.
But I didn't kill him.
He simply lost the game.
Are you still a part of that game?
I'm trying to put an end to it.
How?
I'm going to find that guy first.
The overseer of the game,
who worked for Oh Il-nam.
Do you know who he is?
The masked men call him Captain.
Did you see his face?
No, I didn't see his face.
He was wearing a black mask.
How do you plan on finding him?
This is the invitation he sent.
If you find him, what next?
Kill him?
Killing him
will not put an end to the game.
Before Oh Il-nam died, he said
he created the game for his clients.
That's right.
There are people they call the VIPs.
I saw one of them.
Let me go.
I'll help you find them.
Mr. Seong. You can't trust cops.
I've never seen cops
helping people like us.
I'm sorry about your brother.
But you should forget about it.
Can you forget?
The people who died on that island?
I saw things that you didn't.
I can help you...
with what you're trying to do.
Please reconsider, Mr. Seong.
I once got scammed and lost all my money.
I was furious,
so I roughed him up a little.
It wasn't even that bad,
but the cops only arrested me
and told me to settle with him.
But with what money?
That asshole took everything.
You know what's crazy?
I went to prison, and he got away with it.
Since then, I've never trusted cops...
The money...
Mr. Seong.
So it's true that you won the game?
It's blood money
for all those people who died there.
I'm going to use it
to fight those bastards.
If you help me,
I'll give you as much as you want.
I'm not doing this for money.
Me neither.
That bastard killed my boss
right in front of me.
He was like a brother to me.
He even officiated my wedding.
I'm going to find the fat cats,
tie them up,
make them play Rock, Paper, Scissors
and shoot them dead.
They have armed forces on that island.
We can't fight them with a few pistols.
These are what I've collected so far.
Are they real?
Where did you get all these?
Man, Mr. Seong. So you've got a plan!
I want you to gather people
we can join forces with.
Sure, don't worry.
I know some men
who are good at that stuff.
These are K2s, aren't they?
I haven't seen one
since I was in the military.
I'm guessing they're black market.
Do they even work?
Come and practice whenever you can.
Also,
I suggest that you quit your current job.
God, it's hot. Turn up the AC!
Man, why is the AC here so weak? Damn it.
- Can somebody ask to get it fixed?
- The weather is insane.
- I want to go home.
- What are you doing after work?
- Want to grab a beer?
- Sounds good.
- I'm in.
- A new place opened nearby.
- I'm exhausted.
- That was rough.
Bunny, this is for you.
Bunny, does it hurt here?
It's too hot for this, man.
I can't breathe in this fucking pig head.
Is it just me?
Na-yeon!
Na-yeon.
I told you not to go into random places.
Daddy!
Don't cry. I'm sorry, guys.
You're okay. Daddy is here.
When did she get out of the hospital?
Who is she?
You know the artists
who draw people's portraits in the park?
That guy is one of them,
and she's his daughter.
Is she sick?
Well, I hear she has blood cancer.
Apparently, she needs
a bone marrow transplant,
but it's not easy to get one.
SANG-WOO'S FISH STORE
- Take care.
- Thank you. Bye.
Cheol!
Grandma.
- Have you had dinner?
- Yes.
I had a burger with my friends.
That's not enough.
I steamed some sweet potatoes.
Sweet potatoes? But I'm full.
Drink some sikhye then.
The woman next to Sae-byeok is her mom.
She was recently released from
a prison camp in North Hamgyong Province.
How is she doing?
There was a tuberculosis outbreak
in her prison,
but she never received proper treatment.
She won't be able to move for a while.
Please just get her here
as soon as possible.
I've got the best experts ready
in China and North Korea.
As soon as she recovers,
we'll get her moving.
I can give you more money
if that's what you need.
No.
You've already given me enough money.
After last time, I owe it to Sae-byeok.
I'm going to make this happen.
What's this?
SANG-WOO'S FISH STORE
That's where
Sae-byeok's little brother is.
If you can't get in touch with me,
please contact this number.
All right, I will.
Oh, for God's sake. You again?
Why do you keep bothering me like this?
I told you to find another broker.
Everyone else says she's dead.
Then she must be dead.
Do you think I can magically
bring people back to life?
You said she might be alive.
No, what I meant was
no one has actually witnessed her death
or found her body.
I wasn't saying that she's alive.
No one has seen her alive either.
Please look for her one last time.
Why is everyone offering me money?
I knew being kind has its rewards.
Please give it another try.
If this isn't enough,
I'll bring you more money.
If this was about money,
I would've asked for it a long time ago.
No-eul, you know
how hard I've tried to find her.
I felt bad for you
because I'm a father myself.
- I really did my best.
- I hear you.
Please, one last time.
Let me be honest with you.
How do you expect a one-year-old
to survive in North Korea
without her parents?
Besides, her mother shot her superior
and defected
to South Korea like a traitor...
I'm not saying it was your fault, No-eul.
That's just what happened.
I know it's harsh to tell a mother
to forget about her child,
but you really should.
There's nothing else you can do.
I'm sorry. I'll move my car right away.
Ms. Kang No-eul.
Hi, Mother.
Where are you? Are you there yet?
I'm walking up there now.
Jun-ho. Take a look and see
if your brother has visited.
If he's alive, he would've left flowers
on the anniversary of his wife's death.
Did he come by?
No.
I suppose your brother
doesn't want us in his life anymore.
We haven't heard from him in years now.
It's probably because
he still resents me deep down.
We were also struggling back then,
and he knows that.
I just don't want him to think
that I favored you over him
because he's my stepson.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Please stop thinking that.
He knows that's not true.
Your brother...
He saved your life
by giving you one of his kidneys.
But when his wife got sick,
I couldn't do anything for her.
If I could have...
I would've sold my organs to help her.
If that were the issue,
he'd resent me instead.
If he hadn't given me his kidney,
he could've sold it
and gotten her the treatment she needed.
If I had just died--
Don't say such a thing.
Neither should you!
Stop saying these things!
Fate gave her that disease,
and it was In-ho's own decision
to take bribes.
You and I are not responsible
for what happened to him!
He simply paid for what he had done.
I'm sorry.
RESIGNATION LETTER
It's for personal reasons.
Still, you can't quit so suddenly.
It'll be hard to find a replacement.
I'm sorry.
No-eul, how did you work in this thing?
Damn, it's even worse
than the stupid pig head.
Sir, this must be why No-eul is quitting.
Kids might be happy
seeing us in these things,
but it totally sucks
for the adults wearing them.
Isn't that right, No-eul?
We're having dinner together tonight.
You should come and say goodbye.
That's right.
You should join us for dinner.
And have a drink.
Everyone will be sad if you don't.
Thank you for everything.
Man, she's cold.
Right up until her last day.
I've worked with her for over two years,
but we've never even had
a real conversation.
I know. I don't know how she worked
this job with that kind of personality.
Here.
- What happened?
- I found her unconscious.
Na-yeon.
Na-yeon!
Are you with her?
Yes, I'm her father.
Please take her to
Seohyeon University Hospital.
All right. Open up for me.
SEOHYEON UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
PARK NA-YEON
There's a new medication
that's just come out.
It's for patients like Na-yeon
with recurrent cancer or a poor prognosis.
But it's not covered
by insurance at this point.
Doctor, I'll get the money somehow.
Please help Na-yeon.
Make an appointment for tomorrow.
I'll explain the details then.
To run tests...
These guys were in the Marine Corps.
These guys were in UDT.
And these guys were
in the ROK Special Forces.
Oh, and this guy is just a former cop.
As you can see,
they're tough men
who'd go through hell or high water
as long as the pay is right.
Right. This is the leader of the team.
He's a seasoned veteran
who has seen a lot of combat overseas.
Please call me Kim.
You must be careful tomorrow.
If they notice you,
it could ruin everything.
Don't worry.
Only you and I will go into the club.
These guys will be on standby nearby.
Will they even let you in?
Come on, I've already got
the perfect clubbing outfit.
I clean up well.
I'll go in with you.
No.
Your face was exposed on the island.
They might recognize you.
Don't make a move
until I give you the signal.
Understood.
And if something happens to me tomorrow--
Nothing is going to happen.
You've got your tracker.
Wherever you're taken,
we'll be right behind you.
So you can relax. Don't worry!
Dad?
Dad, is that you?
Ga-yeong, who's that?
I don't know. No one's saying anything.
It must be a prank call.
Hang up and come eat
before your soup gets cold.
All right.
If you wish to participate,
please state your name and birthdate.
June 25, 1994.
Kang No-eul.
Confirmed.
Here are the details
for your arranged pickup.
October 31, 2024,
at Tancheon parking lot
under Bongeun Bridge in Songpa-gu, Seoul.
Hey!
Wow, look at all these people.
What is going on today?
OCTOBER 31 MIDNIGHT
CLUB HDH
Wait, is it today?
Hall... What's it called again?
October 31, Halloween.
Yes, Halloween.
I'm getting a bad feeling.
This may be some kind of ruse.
That guy they call the Front Man.
You said he wears a gray hood
and a black mask, right?
Yes.
Oh, that must be why he chose today.
To cover his face.
That bastard is trying to be clever. Damn.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Hold on!
Let me put something over my face.
I'll take this. How much?
We just got in! Can you hear me?
We're underground.
Yes, I can hear you.
And the tracker?
Working fine. What's your status?
It's totally crazy down here!
Everyone is wearing masks,
and I can't tell who's who!
Anyway, I'll let you know
if something happens.
All right.
The masked men are here.
They're going inside.
The masked men?
Hey, everyone here is wearing a mask!
The men in pink jumpsuits from the island!
Really?
What? Do I know you?
What the fuck?
Hey, no cutting.
Go to the back of the line.
Police. Move.
See your fellow officers waiting in line?
It's Halloween.
Go put on your uniform first.
Does this look like a toy?
I don't see any pink jumpsuits!
What?
I just spotted one!
He's taking Mr. Seong somewhere!
I'll follow them!
- There were two of them.
- What? What did you say?
- There were two of them!
- What?
Mr. Choi, where are you?
Mr. Choi!
They left the club. Get ready!
Guys, it's time to roll.
Get ready.
He just got into a white limo.
All teams, tail them.
We have to catch him. Keep that in mind.
Go.
Player 456.
Do you remember?
We once spoke in this car.
Was it this car?
It's nicer than I remember.
I sincerely hoped you'd have a good life.
I hoped you'd forget everything
that happened and be happy.
I didn't know you cared so much about me.
I'm almost moved to tears.
You should have gotten on that plane.
That's the best choice
you could have made.
I have never forgotten...
what you said to me then.
That's why I wanted
to see you again so badly.
Now that we're here,
say what you want to say.
What do you want from me?
Stop the game.
The game?
The game you've been playing.
The game
that's still going on to this day.
All we did was create it.
All of you participated by choice.
Don't give me that shit.
You manipulate people
who feel like they're at a dead end.
You drive them to their deaths
and enjoy it.
You think if you just call it
their own choice,
your filthy game will become
some sort of charity event?
They were all just losers of the game.
Trash eliminated from the competition.
A ton of new trash is being poured
into the world as we speak.
You still don't see, do you?
The game will not end
unless the world changes.
Do you have the limo in sight?
Yes, we see it.
It's on Seogang Bridge,
headed toward Yeouido. What now?
Don't do anything yet.
It has to be somewhere less crowded.
Understood.
"That's just how the world is,
so just shut up and accept it"?
That's a story created by people like you.
You think people are just
horses in a race,
and you own the horses.
Your way with words has improved.
So? Is your plan to convince
the owners of the horses?
To stop the race?
We're on it now.
But the limo's movements seem suspicious.
How so?
It's circling the Yeouido area.
They might have caught on already.
Stop the limo now!
Roger. Initiating the plan.
Shit!
What the hell?
What's going on?
One of the tires blew out.
Shit. Team Two will follow them.
- Okay. Back the car up now!
- Back up.
There's a sniper. Get down!
Both teams are under attack.
We have to abort the operation.
Or were you going to kidnap me?
I'll follow them.
They got me.
I'm losing them.
Stop the car.
Do you think you can stop the game
with a pistol?
Put me in the game.
You want to be in the game?
Put me back in the game.
Weren't you telling me
to stop the game just a second ago?
If I'm back in the game,
those fat cats you serve
will find it fun for sure.
So,
take me to the games.
What are you hesitating for?
Are you scared?
That you might lose to me
like Oh Il-nam did?
Oh Il-nam didn't want to admit it
until the moment he died.
He knew someone had come
to help that homeless man,
but he refused to look out the window.
But
when he stopped breathing,
I'm sure he knew
that he had lost.
Have you seen The Matrix?
They could've lived in peace
if they took the blue pill.
But they still chose the red pill
to play the heroes.
Do you also think you're a hero
who can change the world?
I'll show you
that the world...
doesn't always go
the way you want it to.
If that's what you want, have it your way.
Player 456.
Welcome back to the game.
We will now initiate plan B.
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song