Official Kisskh movies site:
Kisskh.love
You motherfucker!
Fuck!
Motherfucker! Fucking X bastard!
Damn you!
Fuck you! You fucking loser!
- You fucker!
- Fucking asshole! Die!
SQUID GAME 2
EPISODE 7
FRIEND OR FOE
The following players
have been eliminated.
Players 230, 268,
299, 331, and 401.
End of list.
What's going on?
Listen, Team O!
We...
When we were in the bathroom,
those fucking X bastards
tried to kill all of us!
They killed some of us,
including my friend--
Bullshit.
You're the ones who started it.
Damn it.
They threatened one of the people
on our side!
They attacked us to win the second vote!
That's right!
Hey.
You killed one of us first.
You were trying to win the vote
by killing us!
Fuck you. You killed some of us too.
Did you think we would
just let you kill the rest of us?
So?
Which side lost more people?
What?
All right, everyone!
Let's count the numbers!
Yeah, that's right!
Let's count ourselves! Come on down!
Everyone! Gather round!
We need everyone down here! Come on!
- Get down here now!
- Gather round!
- Come on!
- Get down here!
- Gather round!
- Form a line!
- Please come down!
- Captain?
- Huh?
What are you doing here?
Oh, well...
Isn't that my drone?
What? Oh, this?
Well, I was looking for something
because I couldn't sleep,
and I just stumbled across it.
Did you do something?
No, I was just looking.
I'm fascinated by
how this thing can fly in the sky.
All right. I'm done now.
It's so fascinating.
You reek of alcohol.
Go get some sleep now, okay?
Stop!
Who are you really?
You son of a bitch!
Who's there?
Choi, is that you?
It's me, Captain Park.
Captain, I thought you were asleep.
What are you doing out here?
It's pouring down.
I couldn't sleep.
I was tossing and turning,
then I heard some noise.
I heard it too.
I think I heard someone scream
and some thuds after that.
That's why I came out to take a look.
I think it was the waves hitting the deck.
Look at the mess.
Oh, you're right.
It's dangerous out here in the rain.
Go back inside and get some sleep.
The boat's rocking so much.
I can't really sleep.
Still, you've got to wake up early.
Try to get some sleep.
Or you'll be exhausted tomorrow.
41, 42, 43, 44, 45,
46,
47.
Three dead.
Are you sure?
I counted three times.
What about them?
42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48.
Two people died on our side.
Two out of five.
That means they lost three people.
Then we have a better shot
at winning the vote tomorrow.
Hey, it's 48 against 47.
As long as we don't change our minds,
we'll win by one vote!
Yes!
- We'll win.
- We can get out of here tomorrow.
Attention, please.
Lights out in 30 minutes.
All players, please return to your beds
and prepare for bedtime.
Listen. You cannot change your minds.
We have to win the second vote
and get out of here tomorrow. All right?
Don't worry. We're determined to get out.
That's right.
We really have to get out now.
Yes, let's do this.
All right.
Let's go to sleep now, shall we?
The delivery team has set out.
How are the goods?
In top condition this time.
And Number 011?
That bitch is behaving.
Won't be a problem anymore.
Keep watching her carefully.
Yes, sir.
Get ready.
The special game will begin momentarily.
Managers, soldiers, and workers,
please move to your designated locations.
Let me repeat.
The special game will begin momentarily.
Managers, soldiers, and workers,
please move to your designated locations.
Lights out in 20 minutes.
All players, please prepare for bedtime.
Those bastards are acting suspicious.
It looks like they're up to something.
Whatever those idiots do,
once we win the vote tomorrow,
it'll all be over.
You think we'll be okay?
They say things were really crazy
in the bathroom earlier.
Once the lights go out,
people on the other side will attack us.
Really?
Because if they kill us, they'll be able
to win the vote and increase the prize.
So what do we do?
Let's attack them first.
They're probably thinking
we'll just wait for the second vote.
We can use it to our advantage.
We'll attack them first
once the lights go out.
That's right.
It'd be better to attack them first.
We have more women
and elderly on our side.
If we get attacked,
we'll be at a disadvantage.
Attacking them first
would give us a better chance of winning.
- I agree.
- We can't do that.
But we have to get out of here.
You said it yourself.
Staying calm won't get us anywhere now.
That doesn't mean
we should kill each other.
That's exactly what they want us to do.
"They"?
The ones who created this game.
The ones who watch us play.
If we're going to fight someone,
it should be them.
Where are they?
Up there.
On the upper levels
are the rooms they control the games from.
The man in the black mask is their leader.
Once we capture him, we'll be able to win.
How are you going to fight them?
They have guns.
All armed soldiers,
please move to your designated locations.
The special game will begin momentarily.
We'll fight them with guns too.
But we don't have any.
We'll take their guns.
From those masked men?
That's too dangerous.
Even if we manage to take a few guns,
we'll still be outnumbered.
What then?
Are you going to kill each other all night
and hope you survive?
Is that what you want, Young-il?
Do we...
stand a chance?
We do if we catch them off guard.
Out of everyone,
they're the ones
who would least expect us to attack first.
This is
our last chance
to end these games once and for all.
How are you going to take their guns?
Once the fight begins tonight,
we'll have our chance.
Lights out in five minutes.
Thanos, that fucking asshole.
That son of a bitch
treated me like a fucking idiot.
Myung-gi.
When the lights go out, hide.
No matter what happens, don't do anything.
Okay.
And wipe that blood off.
Lights out in ten seconds.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Once the lights go out,
get under the bottom beds quietly.
You must not get caught
by those planning to attack us.
Shut up!
Die!
We have to hide until the fight ends.
Don't get caught up in the fight.
But that would put people on our side
at quite a disadvantage.
Without us in the fight,
they'll be outnumbered.
I know.
But if we fight with them
and some of us end up dead or injured,
it will ruin our entire plan.
We can't beat those bastards
with a lower headcount.
Are you suggesting that
we make a small sacrifice
for the greater good?
If we miss this opportunity,
the sacrifice will be even greater.
Even if it takes a sacrifice...
we must put an end to this game now.
In that case,
I'm with you.
The fight won't last long.
Because if all of us end up hurt or dead,
there can't be a next game,
and they wouldn't want that.
Se-mi.
You fucking bitch.
Fuck!
You goddamn bastard!
You fucking bitch!
You think you're better than me?
Suppress!
Prepare.
Suppress.
Once the lights come on,
the soldiers will come
to settle the situation.
Hands up. Get back.
They'll try to break up the fight first.
Drop your weapon. Hands up.
They won't pay attention to the dead.
- They will scan our trackers...
- Check the IDs of the dead.
...to identify us.
That'll be our window.
Dae-ho!
Have everyone retreat and close the gate.
Retreat.
Stop! Hold fire!
Everyone, hold fire!
Hands above your head!
On your knees!
You goddamn bastards!
No!
Move! Do you not see this?
They are not human.
They're like goddamn vermin
blinded by money!
This is not what we took these guns for.
If we do this, we'll be no different
from those masked men.
Everyone!
Don't be scared.
Gather round, please!
It's okay to come out.
We're not trying to hurt you!
- Get the guns and ammo from the dead.
- Come on! I have something to say!
Gather all soldiers.
All soldiers, please move
to the assembly point with your weapons.
Let me repeat.
All soldiers, please move
to the assembly point with your weapons.
Everyone.
We will now
head up to the masked men's headquarters.
We'll capture the ones who captured us,
put an end to this game,
and make them pay.
Anyone who knows how to use a gun
and wishes to join us,
please step forward.
Hey.
I know you're scared.
I'm scared too.
But this may be
our last chance
to make it out of this place alive.
Fight with us
so we can go home together.
All together.
I'll fight with you.
Come on.
I'll join you too.
Come join us.
Please check your guns and ammo.
Let's take one radio each.
We'll use channel 7, the lucky number.
Thank you for earlier.
You can buy me a soju when we get out.
Attention.
This is the MP5, a submachine gun.
First, if you press this lever
in the middle and pull the magazine,
it comes off like this.
If the selector switch is down,
it's set to full auto mode.
Up is single-fire mode.
We don't have many magazines,
so set it to single-fire mode.
Lastly, insert the magazine,
pull the handle, and then release it.
That's how you load it. Are we clear?
- Yes.
How do you know so much about guns?
I was a sergeant first class
in the ROK Special Forces.
Take it off.
Take that off too.
Good God.
Do your parents know
what you're doing here?
Take us to your captain.
All players, it is bedtime now.
Please return to your quarters
immediately.
Otherwise,
you will be eliminated from the game.
Let me repeat.
All players, it is bedtime...
I think I'll be hearing this voice
in my dreams. Don't you?
Please return to your quarters
immediately. Otherwise...
Get down!
One o'clock!
Cover me!
Cover!
Hold fire!
Is everyone okay?
- Yes.
- Yes, I'm okay!
All right, then. Let's go up!
Do not let them get close
to the management area.
How much farther?
Is this the right way?
The entrance to the management area
is around that corner.
The control room is right above it.
Move it, then.
Wait.
What are you doing?
I need my mask to pass security.
I'll go look for the management area!
Will you be able to find it?
Should I come?
I'll go with Jung-bae.
I need you to buy us some time!
Jung-bae, let's go.
Wait up!
Here!
Don't waste your ammo like that!
You'll quickly run out!
Identity confirmed.
Why did you have to bring me
instead of Young-il?
Because you're my friend.
You only say that when you're in a jam.
We're in the management area.
We'll make our way up.
They have magazines in their pockets.
Which way should we go?
The way they came.
Guard the stairs to the control room!
This isn't getting us anywhere!
Let's follow them to the upper level!
We might get surrounded
if we move together without a plan!
Let's wait until
they find the control room!
Everyone! Check your magazines!
I'm down to half.
I've got less than half.
Same!
I've got two-thirds left.
I'm almost out!
Mine is empty!
I'm almost out too!
Young-il, Dae-ho. Can you hear me?
Go ahead!
I think we're right below
the control room!
But we need backup and more ammo.
We're running out of ammo too!
There should be spare magazines
in the soldiers' pockets in our quarters.
Go get them!
Got it!
Did you hear that? They need backup!
Three of us will go,
and the rest will stay!
Join us once you get the magazines!
Who wants to go with me?
I'll go!
Me too!
Let's go!
I'll go get the magazines!
I'll come back as soon as I can,
so just hold on until then!
Hyun-ju!
I'll go!
I... I'm out of ammo.
Do you know the way?
Yes.
We destroyed the cameras on the way.
Follow them.
Okay.
Take this. You might run into
the masked men on the way.
Thank you.
I'll cover you. Go!
Cover him!
Magazines in pockets.
Dae-ho.
Can you hear me?
Where are those magazines?
Yes, brother. I'm on my way to get them.
All right, Dae-ho! We're counting on you!
Yes, you can count on me, brother!
I'll be there soon!
Jung-bae, cover me.
What are you going to do?
Get their magazines.
No, that's too dangerous.
I'm almost out of ammo.
If they notice, they'll close in on us.
We need more magazines
to hold out until Dae-ho gets here.
Gi-hun, hurry up!
Hurry up and get back here!
Magazines...
Magazines in pockets.
What's up with him?
I'm not sure.
Dae-ho, what happened?
Why are you back by yourself?
Magazines.
Get the magazines
from those bastards' pockets. Hurry!
Oh, okay.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. It's just a graze.
If you die before me, I'll kill you.
Don't worry. I'll be sure to outlive you.
Gi-hun! Did you find the control room?
I think it's right up there,
but we can't go this way.
I want you to find another way.
I did a quick scan of the layout here.
I'm sure there's a way to go around them.
I want you guys
to keep their focus on you.
We'll hit them from behind.
Okay.
Wait.
Here, take this.
You're going to need it.
Are you sure?
Dae-ho will be back with more.
This was all we could find.
Damn it, what's taking him so long?
Do you think he got lost?
Dae-ho, can you hear me?
Where are you? Can you hear me?
Did you find the magazines?
Are you on your way?
Dae-ho, answer me.
Dae-ho, are you there?
Dae-ho, please answer me!
Dae-ho! Answer me!
We can't hold out much longer.
We need those magazines now.
Something must've happened.
I'll go down and check.
Please do.
Cover me!
Gi-hun, we found it.
Start attacking and draw their attention.
Then we'll hit them from behind.
Okay, got it!
Young-il, what's going on?
Are you attacking?
Gi-hun, I'm sorry.
It's all over.
They got us too.
Young-il, what happened?
Are you all right?
Young-il.
Young-il! Answer me!
Young-il!
Start wrapping things up.
Dae-ho!
Dae-ho, where are you? Dae-ho!
Dae-ho.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
The magazines?
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Get down on the floor!
No.
You can't die like this.
They're moving!
They're coming this way!
We should retreat.
This side is blocked as well.
All players, it is bedtime now.
Please return to your quarters.
Otherwise you will be eliminated
from the game.
No. Don't!
Let me repeat.
All players, it is bedtime now.
Please return to your quarters.
Otherwise...
Let's surrender.
We need to survive somehow.
Advance team, do you copy?
We're out of ammo.
We're surrendering.
Please don't kill--
Please don't kill me.
My daughter is very sick.
I surrender.
Player 456.
Did you have fun playing the hero?
Look closely
at the consequences
of your little hero game.
Gi-hun.
No!
Jung-bae!
Jung-bae...
Player 390, eliminated.
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song