Official Kisskh movies site:
Kisskh.love
Do you think Mr. Seong will be okay?
What if they already did something to him?
They wouldn't have brought him this far
if they wanted to kill him.
Do you think they've taken him
to the island where they play the games?
I'm not sure, but it seems likely.
If I recall,
the island was somewhere in this area.
"If we fail to capture the Front Man,
we infiltrate the island."
That was Mr. Seong's plan B.
It's going according to plan.
Once the games begin,
Mr. Seong's life may be in danger.
We must find him before it's too late.
If I catch those bastards,
I'm going to electrocute their asses.
All right!
If everyone's aboard, let's go!
SQUID GAME 2
EPISODE 3
Player 456.
I sense you're holding on to many things.
You can't leave or stay.
You can't fight it. It's your destiny.
You have souls hovering over your head
who are lingering in this world.
You're not here of your own will.
Those vengeful souls brought you.
If we get out of here,
let me perform a ritual.
I can get rid of all your bad karma.
I would like to extend
a hearty welcome to all of you.
Everyone here will participate
in six different games over six days.
Those who win all six games
will receive a handsome cash prize.
Excuse me.
You said I'd be playing games,
but you practically kidnapped me.
So how can I believe that?
I apologize.
Please understand that it was necessary
to maintain the game's security.
What's with the mask then?
Is your face also a secret?
Yeah! Why are you hiding your face?
Is this some kind of
illegal gambling house?
Even the dealers don't cover their faces
in those places.
To ensure fair gameplay
and confidentiality,
it is our policy not to reveal
the faces and identities of staff.
Please understand.
Did you take off my clothes
and put these on me?
What's with these shoes?
My shoes are limited fucking edition.
They're hard to find!
You going to replace them
if they get ruined?
These don't fit and the color sucks.
Can I just have
what you're wearing instead?
I like pink.
I'm sorry, but that is not possible.
You must be in your uniforms
for the games.
What about my phone?
Why did you take my phone and wallet?
Give them back, please.
We're keeping your belongings safe.
We'll return them once the games are over.
At least give me my phone.
I need to check the crypto market.
If I lose money, will you compensate me?
We will return it to you
once the games are over.
I need to monitor the real-time prices!
Do you know how much I've invested?
Player 333, Lee Myung-gi.
Age 30, used to run a YouTube channel
called MG Coin.
After convincing subscribers to invest
in a new crypto coin called Dalmatian,
causing losses
of approximately 15.2 billion won,
you shut down and disappeared.
You're wanted for fraud
and for violating telecom
and financial investment laws.
Current debt levels, 1.8 billion won.
Player 196, Kang Mi-na,
45 million won in debt.
Player 120, Cho Hyun-ju,
330 million won in debt.
Player 230, Choi Su-bong,
1.19 billion won in debt.
Player 198, Jang do-yeong,
1.4 billion won in debt.
Player 226, Kim Yeong-sam,
1.9 billion won in debt.
Player 444, Kim Nam-du,
2.02 billion won in debt.
Player 343, Sim Jae-seok,
2.89 billion won in debt.
Player 006, Park Mi-hwa,
3.1 billion won in debt.
Player 283, Lee Eun-ju,
4.02 billion won in debt.
Player 100, Im Jeong-dae,
ten billion won in debt.
One more game!
Ten billion? Who's that?
Who is it?
What are you looking at?
Do you think it's easy
to get a ten-billion-won loan?
They don't lend
that kind of money to just anyone!
Only to those
who are capable of paying it back.
All of you in this room
have crippling debts
and are now on a cliff-edge.
When we first came to you,
you did not trust us either.
But as you know, we played a game
and gave you money as promised.
And so you trusted us
and volunteered to participate
according to your own free will.
You have one last chance to decide.
Do you want to live like a piece of trash,
running from creditors?
Or will you seize
the last opportunity we are offering?
Getting closer.
I think it's one of those islands ahead.
Captain, let's pick up the speed.
Sure, as you wish.
What you see now
is the piggy bank where
your valuable prize money will be stored.
After each of the six games you will play,
the prize money will accumulate
in this piggy bank.
How much is the prize money?
The prize money for the games
is 45.6 billion won in total.
45.6 billion won?
And one of us will get it?
We will give you the details
about the distribution of the prize money
after the first game.
For these games,
you will be given a special new advantage.
What is it?
After each game,
you will be given a chance
to vote on whether
to continue the games or not.
If the majority votes to stop the games,
you can leave with the prize money
accumulated up to that point.
Are you saying
we'll still receive the money,
even if we leave after the first game?
That is correct.
Good heavens. Excuse me.
You idiot!
Mom! What... What are you doing here?
That's what I wanted to ask you!
What are you doing here?
You're embarrassing me.
Embarrassing?
If you knew what was embarrassing,
you wouldn't be here!
Stop it! We'll talk about this later.
No, we won't. Come on, you're leaving.
You're leaving now, okay?
Mom, why did you come here?
Do you realize where you are?
This is no place for an old lady!
Why did I come here?
To pay off your debt, of course!
Do you even have to ask?
You fool.
Why would you bring
a naive old woman here?
Will you take responsibility
if my mom collapses?
Yong-sik, I'll stay and do this.
You go home.
Stop it! I'm already here.
I can't just leave.
But you promised me.
You promised never to gamble again!
No, this isn't gambling.
We're just playing games here.
I'll just play one game and go.
You idiot, it's the same thing.
- Be quiet! That's enough!
- Don't you dare.
- Are you kidding me?
- They're just games! Right, everyone?
If you wish to participate in the games,
please sign the player consent form.
Those who do not wish to participate,
please speak up now.
We always give you a chance
to leave the games.
You'll really pay us
even if we play just one game?
Mom, you can't play any games.
Just go home!
If you're not leaving, neither am I.
- I'm not going anywhere without you.
- Will you hurry up?
The amazing Myung-gi from MG Coin?
Is that you?
Who are you?
You may not know me, but I know you.
MG Coin.
I was subscribed to your channel.
And I lost a shitload of money, asshole.
So did I.
You've got the wrong person.
I watched your content all day, every day.
Now I even see you in my dreams, motherfucker.
- Was your name Nam-su?
- It's Nam-gyu.
- From Club Pentagon.
- Right.
Thanks to you,
I bonded quickly with Nam-gyu here.
Because we shared the same pain.
I thought the sons of bitches
who made that coin
fled to the Philippines with the money.
So why are you here?
Did they cut you loose?
What do you want from me?
What do you think? Give me my money.
Did I force you to buy that coin?
You told us to bet it all, you fucker.
You swore it'd shoot up.
You said we'd be fucking idiots
if we didn't buy it!
"You are responsible for
the final decision on your investment."
Didn't you hear me say that at the end?
You said you watched every day.
- Hey, calm down!
- You asshole.
- All right now!
- Get off me.
Let go of me.
People are watching.
You don't want to be on the news.
You'd better do well
because I'm coming to get my money back.
Come on.
PLAYER CONSENT FORM
1. A PLAYER IS NOT ALLOWED
TO VOLUNTARILY QUIT THE GAMES
2. A PLAYER WHO REFUSES TO PLAY
WILL BE ELIMINATED
3. THE GAMES MAY BE TERMINATED
UPON A MAJORITY VOTE
IN CASE OF A TIE,
PLAYERS WILL VOTE AGAIN
4. IF THE GAMES ARE TERMINATED,
PLAYERS WILL DIVIDE THE PRIZE EQUALLY
SIGNATURE
Those who do not wish to participate,
please speak up now.
SEONG GI-HUN
A man shouldn't go back on his word.
You said you were giving up.
I'm sorry.
It was urgent,
and you were the only person I could call.
You showed up out of the blue
with those men in black.
What the hell is going on?
In case you've forgotten,
I'm the captain of this boat.
Tell me what the situation is.
I got a lead on where the island is.
And what is it?
I found someone who played the games.
- Really?
- Yes.
But it looks like
he's been taken back there.
We're tracking his location.
Detective Hwang!
My device is telling me
it's that island over there!
Are you familiar with it?
Yeah, people used to live there.
Nowadays, people just go there to fish
from time to time.
It seems like it may be the right place.
If it is, there should be
roads for vehicles
and facilities like a helicopter pad.
I'll fly the drone over and see.
You should go ashore
and follow the tracker.
Okay. Listen up! Get ready to disembark!
The first game will begin momentarily.
Smile.
After having your picture taken,
follow the staff's instructions
and proceed to the game site.
You're Thanos, the rapper.
Oh, shit.
Please look into the camera.
I'm gonna kill half of humanity
With my raps, bam
The runner-up
of The Rap Battleground final.
I'm Gyeong-su, big fan.
I've been to several of your concerts.
Please take a picture with me.
- Me too!
Hang on, guys!
Let's make this easier on Thanos
and take one picture together.
Would that be okay?
- All right, let's get together.
- It's Thanos!
Hey, I don't mind
having one more person. Come on.
Smile.
Are we all in the shot?
You are not allowed to do this.
You want to be in the picture? Come on.
You must take your photos one by one.
Come on, can't you make an exception?
You took our phones,
and we can't take any pictures.
No.
When we get out of here,
I'll take a picture with each of you.
- Okay. Guys, let's go.
- All right! Sweet!
Please look into the camera.
Smile.
Is that a man or a woman?
There are people like that.
They're men who want to be women.
Why would they want to be women?
Men are men, and women are women.
You can't say things like that.
Good grief, that's unsightly.
Please look into the camera.
Smile.
What?
Gi-hun!
Jung-bae.
Fuck, you were alive this whole time?
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
No one's heard from you for three years.
I heard your mom passed away.
I had to hear about it from my wife!
What kind of friend are you?
Were you going to cut me out
because I didn't lend you money?
Keep moving! Don't block the way.
It's not like that.
It's a long story.
Right. I can imagine,
seeing as you're here.
Still, you should've told me
about your mom.
You know how much she liked me.
Why are you here?
What about your wife?
We got divorced.
Divorced?
What about your kid?
With my wife.
Why? I thought you guys were doing okay.
Did you have an affair?
Yeah, like I could manage one.
Let's not talk about it here.
When we get out,
let's go for a drink and talk.
Jung-bae. Whatever happens from now on,
stay close to me.
"Stay close"? You've gotten melodramatic.
Just do as I say!
You must stay close behind me!
All right, man. I will.
Like this? Like Follow the Leader?
By the way, this is crazy.
What is this place?
This way!
Start from the coast. Keep it low.
Got it.
Damn.
- Welcome to the first game.
- My legs! That was a lot of stairs.
All players,
please wait a moment on the field.
Let me repeat.
All players,
- please wait a moment on the field.
- Hey, señorita.
Don't you know who I am?
Do I have to?
No, you don't.
We can get to know each other.
Tell me about yourself.
Are you hitting on me?
In the sea of faces, you caught my eye
My beauty, my flower blooming among weeds
Red, orange, yellow, green
I'm a legend, Thanos
Look at us in this blue-green
Now give me the green light
I like you!
What's that?
What's that thing?
Damn, this isn't built for us to walk on.
I found him! Over there!
The first game is Red Light, Green Light.
- We're playing Red Light, Green Light?
- See?
We're playing games, not gambling.
This is a children's game.
Red Light, Green Light? The kids' game?
Hey, you.
Me?
What... What are you doing?
- Damn it.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Freeze. Don't move.
- Who the hell are you?
Do not move.
What are you doing?
Is that your dental implant?
Where is it?
Damn it.
I'm fucked.
- Where did you get this?
- Get what?
Why was this in here?
That? Before I got on the boat here,
some guy said he had leftover bait
and gave that to me. Why?
Detective Hwang, we're screwed.
They're onto us.
They put the GPS tracker on someone else.
We are ready to start the game.
Start.
Cross the finish line in five minutes
without getting caught.
- If you do, you pass.
- Everyone!
Everyone, listen up! Pay attention!
Listen carefully!
This is not just a game!
If you lose the game,
you die!
What is he saying?
Hey! What are you talking about?
We're going to die
playing Red Light, Green Light?
- Red light...
- Yes, that's right!
If they catch you moving,
they will kill you!
They will shoot you from somewhere!
That guy must be drunk.
- Stay on your toes!
- He says they'll shoot us if we lose.
He sounds like my old man
when he gets home drunk
and starts talking crazy.
- Says there's a freaking bug in his head.
- If you get caught, you die!
That doll's eyes are motion detectors!
- See? Talking about devices.
- Stay on your toes!
We might get to join Dad today.
What the hell are you talking about?
I think he's trying to scare us
so he can win the prize money.
That's right!
Don't pull any tricks, asshole!
You have to believe me!
Do not be alarmed or panic!
No matter what happens,
do not panic and start running!
Let the game begin.
Green light, red light.
Freeze!
Well done!
You just need to stay calm like this!
We just have to move
and stop at the right time.
- What's with him?
- Then we can all win.
- We can survive together!
- Do you know him?
No, I don't.
Green light, red light.
Freeze!
Don't move and stay still!
Just relax!
Cut it out. It's you that's scaring me!
Speak with your mouth covered.
It's dangerous.
Green light, red light.
- Why aren't you moving?
- Freeze!
Green light, red light.
Freeze!
- Are you crazy?
- I said cover your mouth!
- Green light, red light.
- Follow me!
Freeze!
Green light, red light.
Nobody move!
Is he high or what?
Nope.
No one is like that when they're high.
You've been high?
You interested?
What's that?
He knows you're a flower.
There's a bee on you.
A bee?
Crap.
I just moved.
Nobody move!
You must not move!
Player 196, eliminated.
Jung-bae.
No matter what happens, don't move.
Do not move!
No! Don't move!
Stay still!
If you run, you'll die!
You will all die if you move!
Don't move! Keep yourselves still!
Don't move, please!
Freeze!
Let me repeat.
You can move forward while the tagger
shouts, "Green light, red light."
If your movement is detected afterward,
you will be eliminated.
Green light, red light.
You'll also die
if you don't make it there in time!
That doll is a motion detector!
But it can't detect motion
that's not visible to it!
Get behind someone bigger than you!
Like you're doing Follow the Leader!
We're running out of time!
We've got to move!
- Get behind me.
- Green light, red light.
Gi-hun.
I'll stay close to you now.
Player 188.
Player 244.
Green light, red light.
Do not move.
Are you okay?
Get close to me.
Do not move!
Freeze!
What the hell?
Bye.
Let's go!
Green light, red light...
It wasn't me.
- She pushed me. I didn't move!
- Player 444.
It was her.
I didn't move.
Player 444, eliminated.
You can do this!
You're almost there!
Green light, red light.
Please help me.
- Green light, red light.
-   Hey! Where are you going?
Please help me.
I'll help you. Get up on this turn.
Green light, red light.
Green...
light...
red light.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Number 011.
Was that you?
I simply took out a loser.
Player 444, eliminated.
Soldiers who have completed your mission,
please line up outside the sniper rooms.
We can't just sit here and do nothing.
We should at least search
some nearby islands.
They led us here, so I don't think
they're anywhere in this area.
A storm warning
has been issued for tonight.
We'd better head back to port.
Damn it.
The search may take a while.
We should go back
and come up with a new plan.
Who leaked the information?
Did one of you get drunk
and blab about it somewhere?
All right, it's getting cold and dark.
Let's get moving.
You're not feeling well?
- Don't worry.
- What?
I'm okay.
Gi-hun. What the hell is that creepy doll?
It shoots people with its eyes.
It's not the doll.
There are shooters.
How do you know so much?
Have you really been here before?
Congratulations for making it
through the first game.
Here are the results of the first game.
Out of 456 players,
91 players have been eliminated.
365 players have completed the first game.
Congratulations again
for making it through the first game.
Sir! Please don't kill us!
Please don't kill us. I beg you!
As for my son's debt,
I will do whatever it takes
to pay you back!
Please forgive us!
Don't just stand there.
Beg for his forgiveness.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
- I promise I'll pay it back!
- There seems to be a misunderstanding.
Please don't kill us!
- Please don't kill us!
- Please spare us!
We are not trying to harm you.
We are presenting you with an opportunity.
Clause three of the consent form.
"The games may be terminated
upon a majority vote."
Correct?
That is correct.
Then let us take a vote right now.
Of course.
We respect your right
to freedom of choice.
But first, let me announce
the prize amount that's been accumulated.
The number of players
eliminated in the first game is 91.
Therefore, a total of 9.1 billion won
has been accumulated.
If you quit the games now, the 365 of you
can equally divide the 9.1 billion won
and leave with your share.
How much is that?
Each person's share would be
24,931,500 won.
Fuck. We almost died,
and they're giving us 24 million?
That's fucking bullshit.
Twenty million?
You said 45.6 billion!
The rule is that
a hundred million won will be accumulated
for each eliminated player.
If you choose to play the next game
and more players get eliminated,
the prize amount
will increase accordingly.
How much will it be
if you survive until the end?
As I already told you,
the total amount of prize money
for all 456 players
is 45.6 billion won.
Those who make it through all six games
will equally divide the 45.6 billion won.
So if you're the only one to survive,
you get 45.6 billion?
That is correct.
45.6 billion? Wow!
So we can take a vote again
and decide to leave after the next game?
As promised in the consent form,
you can take a vote after each game
and decide to leave with the prize money
accumulated up to that point.
We always prioritize
your voluntary participation.
Now, let's begin the vote.
If you wish to continue the games,
press the O button.
If you wish to end them,
press the X button.
The vote will be held
in reverse order of your player numbers.
Player 456.
It's all pointless!
You didn't decide
when to come into this world,
and you can't decide
when you leave it either.
When and where you die
were already decided by the gods
the moment you were born.
No matter how hard you try,
you can never escape it.
Once you finish voting,
put the patch you are given
on the right side of your chest
and stand on the side you have chosen.
Player 454.
Player 453.
Player 390.
Player 388.
Player 380.
Player 333.
Player 332.
Player 246.
Player 230.
Wait a minute, everyone! Wait!
You can't do this.
Come to your senses!
Don't you see?
These aren't just any games.
We will all die if we keep playing!
We have to get out of here now.
With a majority vote, we can!
We must stop here!
Who do you think you are?
Why do you keep
egging people on like that?
You scared us by saying they'd shoot us
before the game even began!
That's right!
He was going on about how we'd die,
and I almost did because I got so nervous!
How did you know
they were going to shoot us?
Are you one of them?
Are you conning us all
by pretending to be a player?
Who is this guy?
Did you plant him to mess with our heads?
That's uncalled for.
We wouldn't have won the game
and survived if it weren't for him!
And you! I saw how scared you were.
Your legs were shaking.
You should thank him,
not treat him like a fraud!
And who the hell are you?
Are you conspiring with him?
Rude. How old are you?
Older than you. What are you going to do?
- Come on now.
- What?
Please don't do this. Listen.
None of us would be alive
if it weren't for this gentleman.
So enough with the greed.
Let's put our lives first
and get out of this place! Okay?
- That's right!
- Let's all get out of here!
- Let's get out of here!
- No, we have to keep playing!
I have played these games before!
I have done this before!
I knew about the first game
because I had played it before!
I played the games here three years ago!
And everyone who was with me...
died here!
- They all died?
- All of them?
- Really? No way.
- Hold on.
If they all died,
how did you survive alone?
Wait, are you saying
you were the sole winner?
That's right.
I was the final winner.
If we continue the games,
every single person here,
just like all the people back then,
will die in the end.
Bullshit.
If you were the sole winner,
it means you won 45.6 billion won.
If you really did,
why would you come back here?
That's right! He's lying!
Cut the crap!
He's a total nutcase!
If someone like you can win, so can I!
If you really won,
it actually works better for us.
You can give us some tips
on how to beat these games.
That's right!
We have a previous winner with us,
so what do we have to worry about?
Come on, let's do this!
- Come on!
- Yeah!
- Let's make some money!
- Let's do this!
- Let's do it!
- Let's try!
Let's make money!
Please, I'm begging you.
We have to get out now!
If we keep playing, more people will die.
That could be you.
We have to stop this now
and get out of here.
Everyone.
From here on, we will not tolerate actions
that disrupt the voting process.
Now, let's resume the vote.
Player 228.
Player 100.
Player 007.
Yong-sik!
Don't get any stupid ideas.
That's right!
Player 006.
Player 004.
Lastly, Player 001.
Everyone, say O!
- O!
- X!
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song