Official Kisskh movies site:
Kisskh.love
- One, two.
Go. Get it.
All right, throw it hard.
Fail.
Come on, again. Smash it!
All right.
Fail.
What are you doing?
Pick it up and throw it!
Hang on, Young-mi.
Try it with the other side.
The other side.
Go. Here we go.
Pass.
Great job.
- Yes! All right!
- You did it!
- Well done. Let's go.
- Thank God!
Ready, go!
I can't watch. It's making me anxious.
Okay.
There.
- I'm sorry!
- It's okay.
All right, we'll go pick it up.
All right, now walk backwards.
We could save some time
walking backwards like that.
They're actually faster going backwards.
All right.
Here we go. Come on.
Yong-sik, look.
Imagine the stone is the face
of the crook who scammed you.
That asshole ruined my fucking life!
Pass.
Way to go!
They can do it.
Old hag! What are you doing--
You said you played Gong-gi
with bullets during the Korean War.
Mom, just imagine
the stone is Dad's mistress' face.
Rotten bitch!
- Pass.
- She did it! Go!
Dad!
All right. Ready?
Hurry! One, two!
You have to wrap it around the axle first.
I know.
Don't look at the clock. We've got time.
Are you sure you've done this before?
Stop talking to me.
Take it easy.
- Take it easy.
- Shut her up!
God, it's taking too long.
No, she should do it like...
Dear gods of heaven and earth,
please have mercy on me.
Dear...
The gods of heaven and earth
have abandoned us.
- She's completely out of it.
- She can't be.
They've abandoned us.
Am I going to die here?
Get yourself together.
We're all going to die--
If you give up,
I will kill you before your gods do.
Hurry up.
Hurry!
Pass.
- Go!
- Come on!
- Hurry.
- One, two!
Hurry!
You must kick the jegi five times.
Please, look away.
- What?
- Please.
- Yeah, all right.
- You guys too.
Don't look! Turn around, guys!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
- Five!
Pass.
SQUID GAME 2
EPISODE 5
ONE MORE GAME
You motherfucker!
...two, three, four, five!
One, two, three, four, five!
Last teams, get ready.
It's a little sad that
we have no audience, isn't it?
Hey, are you scared?
No, sir!
It's quiet and easier to focus
without anyone watching.
Guys!
We'll see you again at the finish line!
Victory at all costs!
Yes! We'll see each other again!
- Yes, thank you!
- We'll see you again!
- That's right!
- Good luck!
All right. Let's get ready.
I believe in our team.
Plus, we have the previous winner with us.
We're here.
- Pass.
- You did it!
Ready, go!
Okay.
Let's get this done the first time!
I believe in you!
When I played baseball,
my pitches might've been slow,
but I had flawless ball control.
- Yes! You did it!
- Pass.
Ready, go!
I knew you could do it!
Let's stay calm!
All right.
Dae-ho, stay calm. Even if you mess up...
Pass.
That was amazing! Dae-ho, my boy!
- Come on, let's go.
- Let's go!
Ready, go!
We've got plenty of time!
You're expecting, so be careful.
There's no rush. Take your time.
Damn, we might get through everything
on the first attempt.
It's okay, we've got enough time.
Let's go pick it up. Ready, go.
No fun passing everything without a hitch.
That's right.
You can't grow without failure, right?
Now backwards. Ready, go.
- God.
- All right.
It's okay. Just stay calm.
Excuse me.
Fail.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's...
Let's go pick it up. All right, let's go.
You sure you did this a lot as a kid?
Throwing it backwards, now that's a skill.
Get up.
Are you taking a break or something?
Now forward. Ready, go!
Hang on.
Let me do this.
What the hell is the problem?
Stay calm, okay?
Don't rush it. No!
- Damn it!
- Fail.
- We still have time--
- What the hell is wrong with me?
You goddamn idiot! You're an idiot!
No one is blaming you!
All right. Take a deep breath, okay?
Try to remember the times
when you had fun playing this.
Now, deep breaths.
Deep breaths. Calm down.
It's okay.
Take your time, okay? Stay calm.
All right.
Let's go! Ready, go!
How are you holding up?
Are you okay?
Okay, move.
One, two, three, four...
You did it!
- Pass.
- Let's go!
Ready, go!
One, two! Quickly!
We're almost there!
- We did it!
- Well done!
The following players
have been eliminated.
Players 135, 239,
263, 415...
Fuck, way too many are still alive.
Hey.
How many do you think are left?
Sorry?
How many roaches
do you think we have left in here?
About 200.
How do you know?
What are you, an AI bot?
Go count them.
Now?
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
Why do you want to count them?
Are you stupid?
The masked men will come and tell us soon.
Shut up, bitch.
Stop it.
- What's your name again?
- It's Min-su.
How old are you?
I'm 27.
So you were born in 1997.
Why do you treat him like he's your boss?
He's the same age as you.
- Nam-su, isn't that right?
- It's Nam-gyu.
- Yes, Nam-gyu. Isn't that right?
- Yes.
You're the same age.
Treat him like a friend.
We'll work better as a team that way.
Okay?
How old are you?
Born in 1998.
You?
Born in 1996.
It's settled.
Gyeong-su is the youngest,
you're the same age, and you're older.
Hey, call her noona since she's older.
Do it.
Unnie.
Can I ask you something?
Yes.
How did you know it'd be easier
to flip the ddakji with the other side?
I used to play Ddakji
with my friends when I was a kid.
And that was my secret trick.
I see.
Listen, can I ask you something too?
Yes.
When you were playing Jegi,
how come you didn't want us to look?
Oh.
Well, I...
Are you shy?
It's not that.
I'm just not completely done.
What do you mean?
Mom, stop asking questions.
You're being nosy.
It's all right.
I still have some procedures left.
I just didn't want people to stare at me.
What procedures?
Oh, so that's how
you got yourself those too?
Of course. I knew they were too big--
Mom, please!
I'm so sorry.
What? We have more survivors?
It's that nutjob's team.
Goddamnit. There's going to be a big drop
in the prize money they add.
- That young lady made it.
- Who?
The tiny young lady.
They don't seem so happy to see us.
That sweet old lady.
I miss my mom.
The day's work has been completed.
All soldiers,
please proceed to your quarters.
I thought you'd be a total freak,
but you actually have a decent face.
North Korean girls are pretty.
What the hell is this?
You're breaking the rules.
Rules, my ass.
You should've steered clear
if you weren't going to help.
I'm going to report this.
To whom? The officer?
How long do you think he'll protect you?
He's already cut you loose.
Do you want me
to explain it to you in detail?
The situation you're in right now?
Fuck. You damn commie.
Shall I ruin your face?
Or shall I cut your fingers off
so you can't pull the trigger anymore?
Last warning.
If you get in our way again,
I will cut off all your fingers
and throw them in the incinerator.
And play with you a little too.
I'm sorry about earlier, everyone.
No, it's okay.
Don't be.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have made the last kick.
Player 222, are you feeling all right?
Yes.
Thank you all
for letting me be on your team.
She smashed that ddakji
and flipped it on her first try.
That was impressive.
She did great, even while carrying a baby.
We were lucky she joined our team.
What about your Flying Stone play?
You hit it with one shot.
With an underhand pitch at that. Bam!
You were like Kim Byung-hyun.
And you? Was Gong-gi
the only game you ever played?
I could barely see your hand.
It was like a martial arts movie.
I'm the only son for two generations.
My mom only let me play at home
with my sisters.
And yet they let their precious son
join the Marines?
My father's idea,
he wanted me to be more of a man.
He fought in the Vietnam War, you see.
- He sounds like a great man.
- Yeah.
Was he a Marine too?
Yeah, well...
Would you excuse me for a moment?
Listen. Perhaps we should learn
each other's names.
I still don't know your names, gentlemen.
Or yours, Miss.
I'll start. I'm Kang Dae-ho.
"Dae" means "big," "ho" means "tiger."
"Big tiger." Cool name.
My name is Park Jung-bae.
"Righteous" and "twice."
My parents wanted me
to be twice as righteous.
My name is Kim Jun-hee.
I don't know what it means though.
Jun-hee. When you get out of here,
go see a doctor right away.
You've been under a lot of stress.
You need to get yourself checked out.
Okay.
I'm Oh Young-il.
-"Young-il"?
- Yes.
"Young-il" sounds like "zero one,"
and that's my number.
Easy to remember.
Oh, that's true! Your name is your number.
Oh, Gi-hun. What's your last name?
My name is Seong Gi-hun.
- I see.
- Seong Gi-hun.
"Seong" literally means "last name."
Congratulations to all of you
for making it through the second game.
Here are the results of the second game.
In the second game,
110 players were eliminated.
The prize money accumulated
up to this point is 20.1 billion won.
Since there are 255 players remaining,
each person's share is 78,823,530 won.
Wait, what?
It's still under 100 million?
It's not even 80 million.
Only 110 people died? Is that all?
Did you count them right?
That's all? But you shot all those people!
- It was more than that!
- Count them again!
Fuck. I almost died twice,
and that's all I get?
I'd get more money than that
if I let somebody beat me up!
I completely understand
your disappointment.
However, we always keep the door open
for you to pursue new opportunities.
You will now take a vote to decide
whether to continue the games or not.
Whether to continue the games
for a bigger prize or to stop here
is entirely your choice.
Please feel free
to exercise your right to choose
in a democratic manner.
- Yong-sik.
- Yeah?
If we go home today,
let's have kimchi stew.
I'll make it with some aged kimchi.
With a lot of pork, right?
I suddenly feel hungry.
Listen, I think it's more than
a coincidence that we met here.
If we get out, I'd like to invite you
to our house for a meal.
We'll grill some pork belly.
Would that be okay?
Absolutely!
We live in a small place, but there is
enough space for four people to eat.
There's space for you to lie down.
You can sleep over.
Unnie, are you coming?
By the way, where do you all live?
We live in Bongcheon-dong.
Really? I live in Sillim-dong.
Goodness, we're practically neighbors!
What about you, Hyun-ju?
Do you live in Seoul?
I live in Gwangmyeong.
My! That's only a 30-minute bus ride away.
I'm surprised we all live
so close together.
We must have a special connection.
This is amazing.
Don't worry.
I want to stop here too.
I should go and be with my wife
at the hospital.
I'm telling you. We'll get out this time.
Damn it.
A Marine should think strategically
and know when to retreat.
Isn't that right, brother?
Yeah, you're right.
Marines aren't invincible.
We should get out.
We have to end the games here.
I will help you guys out when we get out.
Please trust me and support this vote.
Guys, all huddle up again.
- In 1, 2, 3. Victory at all costs!
- Victory at all costs!
This time,
the vote will begin with Player 001.
Player 001, please cast your vote.
Player 006.
Player 007.
Excuse me.
Yong-sik.
Don't get any foolish ideas.
If we put our money together,
it'd be over 150 million.
We'll pay off your debt with it
and use the rest to open
a produce store or something. Okay?
Hurry up! Are you doing a goddamn ritual?
Shut your mouth!
Don't betray us.
What?
- This.
- Player 048.
We all agreed
to play one more game, right?
Yeah.
Player 125.
Player 126.
Excuse me.
Everyone!
Are you all out of your minds?
You still want to keep going
after watching all those people die?
Who's to say you won't die
in the next game?
We have to stop.
We'll all die if we keep going!
Come to your senses,
and leave with that money.
You've got to survive first,
or there won't be a next step.
What do you think
we can do with a mere 70 million?
I don't know how much you owe,
but for most people here,
that doesn't even cover 10% of their debt.
Am I right?
There's no next step for us!
That money won't change anything!
- Yes, he's right!
- That's right!
With that amount of money,
I won't last long.
It was 25 million after the first game,
and now it's 78 million!
After one game,
the amount more than tripled!
If we play one more game,
the prize will be at least 240 million!
But I can't do this anymore.
Please.
Please let me out of here.
I really...
I really want to go home.
I don't want to die.
Young lady.
You're young, so you'd probably have
another chance.
But I don't.
Please.
My family and I have no future.
My business failed,
and now I owe over 500 million.
I've got to make
at least half of that here
if I want a real shot at a fresh start.
What if you die?
If you die here, your family
won't even get your body.
Then it'd be the end
for you and your family!
- Don't you see?
- Don't get fucking scared!
Ddakji, Red Light, Green Light,
Spinning Top!
It's not like the games
are that difficult.
Look.
There are still 255 players.
Way more than half of us survived!
We've made it this far,
so let's do this one more time!
You make such a good point, young man.
That's right!
We've all played the games well
and are still standing!
Now, let's play one more game!
Just one more, and that's it.
Let's play just one more game!
Yeah, let's play one more game!
One more game!
- One more game!
The results are 139 for O and 116 for X.
Based on the majority vote,
we'll proceed to the third game tomorrow.
Thank you.
Noona.
Aren't you scared?
Scared of what?
Playing more games.
I am scared.
Then why do you want to continue?
Because if I go out now,
I'll have to face even scarier things.
Don't call me noona.
I'm younger than you,
but don't tell those jerks.
Mom. Are you angry?
Don't call me "Mom," you damn fool.
Mom. I'm sorry,
but I can't go home with just that.
What do you mean?
I have a little more debt.
How much?
About 100 million.
I borrowed it from loan sharks
and the gambling den.
If I don't pay them back by next month,
I'll be in huge trouble.
They said they'd take and sell
my eyes, liver, and kidneys.
I know they'll actually do it.
That's why
I haven't been able to come home.
Just one more game.
Next time, I promise I'll vote to leave.
After one more game,
I'll be able to pay off all my debts.
We'll make a fresh start then. Okay?
Yong-sik. "Next time"?
"Fresh start"?
What if one of us gets killed before that?
I know...
maybe you'd be fine without me.
But if something happens to you...
I wouldn't have a reason to live,
even if I make it out of here.
Why would you say such a thing?
We'll get through this together.
Brother!
Brother Jung-bae!
Man...
Hey, just come back here.
- No, I'm good here.
- Oh, come on.
- But... Hey.
- All right.
You should've gone farther away then.
It bugs me seeing you
sitting there all pathetic.
I'm sorry.
Jun-hee, Young-il. I'm sorry.
Gi-hun, I'm sorry.
I borrowed some emergency cash,
and the creditors are harassing
my ex-wife and kid.
If I play one more game,
I think I'll be able to settle my debt.
- So--
- Jung-bae.
You of all people shouldn't have done it.
It's not twice as righteous.
But, looking at the results,
even if you had voted against,
we would still have been outvoted.
Right? It's not entirely my fault.
All right. To be honest,
I understand why you did it.
The money isn't enough for me either,
so when I went up to vote,
I did think about playing one more game.
You did?
I said I get it.
Thank you for understanding.
But I voted in favor
partly because I feel confident.
We did so well as a team, didn't we?
If we stick together one more time,
I'm sure we'll be fine. Jun-hee.
I'll make sure we survive the next game--
"The next game"?
In the next game,
we might have to kill each other.
Gi-hun, that's a bit much.
There's nothing we can do now,
so let's try to stay positive.
We should eat, pull ourselves together,
and try our best again.
Here, Jun-hee. You can have mine too.
Hang in there until the next game.
- No, it's okay.
- Take it.
I don't drink plain milk.
Thank you.
Have my bread too.
I don't deserve to eat.
I'll take your milk then.
It wasn't just me.
Oh, look. See?
I'm not the only one who voted in favor--
Hyun-ju, why did you do it?
We said we were all going
to get together at my house.
Why did you change your mind?
I wouldn't think you'd have
gambling debts like my son.
Is it because of the surgery?
Does it cost that much?
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
I can't even keep
my own child under control,
so who am I to tell you anything?
I...
Everything was fine
until I told people who I really am.
People would look at me strangely,
but I never had any big issues.
But...
once I told people
I wanted to live as a woman
and started transitioning,
everything changed.
My mom cried a lot.
And my father stopped talking to me.
I got fired from my job,
and lost all my friends.
I wasn't done with
the treatment and procedures,
but I wasn't earning any money,
so my debt kept piling up.
Although I felt liberated,
my life...
became so much harder.
Oh, dear.
Well, what did you do for work before?
I was in the army.
If you make money here, then what?
Do you have a plan?
I think I'm going to move to Thailand.
Thailand?
I want to play just one more game.
If I win the money...
I'll finish my transition there
and buy a small house.
I want to start a new life there.
I've been to Thailand before.
There are a lot of people
like Hyun-ju over there.
They're hotter and more beautiful
than most women,
and you see them everywhere.
Isn't that right?
Yeah. I hear a lot of them
are really beautiful.
You're beautiful too, unnie.
I don't know if I could say "beautiful,"
but I've spent some time with you now,
and I think you look fine.
You said she was unsightly.
Hey.
You traitor.
How can you take a piss
under these circumstances?
Just finish. You'll get an infection
if you stop mid-stream.
Were you really trying to get out?
What can you even do with 70 million?
That's not even enough to pay me back.
You need to pay me back, and also
compensate for the damage
you did to my soul.
How many times do I have to tell you?
That coin's price did go up.
You held out for more cash
but didn't sell at the right time.
And I have the freedom
to decide if I want to leave.
I don't care for your fucking tone.
Hey, should I just rip his mouth off?
You have the freedom?
- You don't have such a thing.
- Goddamnit.
You're my slave until you pay me back.
My slave.
So you have to keep playing
the games until the end.
And who knows?
You might win the entire prize alone.
Then I will get my money back
And you will get your happiness back
If I won the prize alone,
that'd mean you're dead.
Why would I pay you back if you were dead?
How do you even remember your lyrics?
Oh, right.
You forgot the lyrics
in the show's finale.
You son of a bitch. Got a death wish?
I didn't even eat anything, so why...
I'm watching you.
Are those guys still bullying you?
If they keep doing that,
you can ask for our help.
I'm fine.
Lights out in ten minutes.
- Please prepare for bedtime.
- Pass it to me.
Go under.
Is this really necessary?
I don't like sleeping under there.
Once the lights go out,
somebody might attack us.
What? Who?
The prize money still goes up
if we kill each other.
It's part of the game they designed.
Gi-hun, I think you're overreacting here.
Even if that were true,
people wouldn't do that.
In the previous games,
dozens of people
killed each other at night.
Right here.
You have no idea
how people can change...
in this place.
All right, I guess I didn't know
what I was talking about. I'm sorry.
We need to take turns keeping watch
after lights-out.
I'll take the first watch.
You should decide the order for the rest.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
You always go to the bathroom
in the middle of the night.
Should I come with you?
No. Why would you want to come
to the ladies' room?
Will you be okay alone?
I'm a little scared of the people here.
Look.
Whoa.
- What...
- Listen.
This is the binyeo
your grandmother gave me.
I put it in just in case
I need to protect myself.
If somebody messes with me, I'll just go...
Of course.
Madam Jang Geum-ja,
who survived the Korean War.
Very impressive, ma'am.
Mr. Seong.
I need to use the bathroom.
It's too dangerous to go by yourself.
We can go together.
We need to use the bathroom.
No. Entry and exit
are restricted at this time.
Please. I'm not feeling very well.
No. Entry and exit
are restricted at this time.
Look.
Mr. Triangle.
Even though you're wearing a weird mask,
you're still human, aren't you?
In the outside world,
you might have a sister like her
and a mom like me.
When ladies say
they need to use the bathroom,
it's for reasons they can't tell you.
If you can't understand that,
you shouldn't even call yourself human.
You really shouldn't.
Listen.
Ever since I entered my 60s,
I've had bladder control issues.
I can't go out without wearing a diaper,
but I couldn't bring
any of the things I need here.
Do you really have to make me wet myself?
Imagine if I was your mother,
Mr. Triangle.
You wouldn't do that to your mother.
I came here because of my son's debt.
I should at least get to pee
when I want, shouldn't I?
What did I do
in my previous life to deserve...
Well, thank you.
Can I come too?
Oh, that's okay.
She's a woman. Her name is Hyun-ju.
It's fine. Let's go.
Come quick.
Thank you, Mr. Triangle.
Hold on to me if you need help.
I'm okay.
In a place like this in your condition...
Your mom and dad must be worried sick.
I don't have any.
I have no parents.
Listen.
If you need help with anything,
just let me know.
I'm okay.
Is she sick or something?
She's pregnant.
I think she's almost due.
Gi-hun, I'm up.
You should get some sleep. I'll take over.
I'm not that tired.
Get some more sleep.
I'm sorry.
Let's not talk about it.
I know it wasn't your fault.
No, it's not about that.
I'm sorry I didn't lend you money
when you came to my pub before.
If I had found some way to help you,
your mom might still be alive now.
Man, but I really
didn't have any money then.
I know.
I've never resented you for that.
Is that why you came here before?
To pay for your mom's treatment?
So why did you come back?
If I were you,
I would have put everything behind me
and started a new life with the money.
If...
I died right before your eyes,
and you...
won all the money,
how would you feel?
Come on, don't say that.
We'll make it out together.
That's why I came back.
To make it out with everyone.
To end this game.
But
I don't know anymore.
I don't know what more I can do here.
I ruined your plan
by pressing that button.
I told you it's not your fault.
Hey, do you remember
when we went on strike?
We were occupying the factory,
and management told us to come out.
They said anyone who came out voluntarily
would be let off the hook
and receive more severance pay.
How could I forget?
When I was on night watch,
I wanted to go out. Guess why I didn't.
You were sleeping beside me,
and you were talking in your sleep.
"Mom, I'm hungry. Give me some food."
You were sobbing in your sleep.
- I cried in my sleep?
- Yes.
Asking for food?
Yeah.
So you stayed because of me?
Yeah. I was watching you, and I thought,
"Man, look at this poor little wuss."
"If he wakes up and sees that I'm gone,
he'll start crying and won't even
be able to go the bathroom."
Then I knew I couldn't fucking leave you.
You're so full of shit.
No, I swear on your mom.
Why on my mom? Swear on your own.
Whoever's mom it is, it's true.
I got fired and ended up like this
because I stayed.
You always blame me
for every bad thing that happens,
losing money on the horses
and for your failed chicken shop.
What else? Getting married?
No, I got married because I wanted to.
I got divorced because of you.
Hey, I got divorced because of you.
Because you'd always
invite me out for drinks.
And you're the one
who got me into horse racing.
All right. Quiet down.
You're finally acting like
the Seong Gi-hun I know.
You've been acting like
a different person.
Gi-hun.
After the next game,
let's get out of here, okay?
Let's go drink soju like old times.
You're buying.
People really don't change.
Seong Gi-hun,
the cheapskate of Ssangmun-dong.
The biggest cheapskate.
The king of cheapskates.
"The cheapskate of Ssangmun-dong."
That takes me back.
Is she still in there?
Yes.
Hello? Are you all right?
Are you okay in there? Is something wrong?
Oh, dear. What's wrong?
Are you in pain? Is your belly hurting?
Oh, no. Your baby must be coming.
Listen, tell me where and how it hurts.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
Everything is going to be okay.
You and your baby
are going to be all right.
Don't worry.
Team 2, be careful too.
If you find anything suspicious,
contact us right away.
- Yes, sir.
Captain Park, be careful out there.
Team 2 will search up north.
We'll head out to the southwest.
Okay.
We have to find it in the next four days.
Don't worry.
Captain Ko over there is a local too.
He knows the area inside and out.
And we've got enough fuel
and food for a week.
- Let's give it a go.
- All right.
You've got some soju too, right?
I'll catch some fish with this at night.
You can slice it up nicely for us.
Hey, do you think
you're on a fishing boat?
Stay on your toes
until we find that island.
When it gets dark,
we won't be able to do anything anyway.
What are we supposed to do all night?
Are you going to sing and dance for us?
All right, let's set sail!
The team that finds it first
gets a bonus! Good luck!
- Let's go!
- Good luck!
The third game will begin momentarily.
All players, please get out of bed
and get ready.
Let me repeat.
The third game will begin momentarily.
All players, please get out of bed
and get ready.
Hey, brother. Can I have one too?
You don't want to know.
Once you take it,
you'll never be normal again.
If you get out of here,
don't get involved with them ever again.
Why did you team up with them then?
Because idiots like them
are easier to deal with.
What about me?
Why did you team up with me?
Because...
I thought you wouldn't deceive me.
What?
Anyway, I'm getting out
once the prize money reaches 200 million.
I don't know your situation,
but think carefully.
You won't last long in here.
All soldiers,
please proceed to your stations.
- Wow.
- Yeah!
Young-mi.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We can all win the game
and make it out together.
Welcome to your third game.
The game you will be playing is Mingle.
Let me repeat.
Hey, we'll be mingling together.
Doesn't that sound like so much fun?
All players,
please step onto the center platform.
When the game starts,
the platform will begin to rotate,
and you will hear a number.
You must form groups of that size,
go into the rooms,
and close the door within 30 seconds.
Oh, this game? We used to play
something similar on school trips.
We formed groups by hugging.
Yeah. Instead of hugging,
we go into those rooms.
I know this game.
How should we play this?
Is there a strategy?
If the number is four,
we can stay together.
If it's two, you and me pair up.
If the number is bigger than five,
we'll get the additional people we need.
But what if it's smaller than five?
Like three or four.
We'll figure it out as we go.
No matter what happens, don't panic.
Let's stay calm.
Let's trust each other.
We'll all make it out together. Here.
One, two, three.
- Go!
- Victory at all costs!
Let the game begin.
Round and round
Let's go around in circles and dance
We will clap our hands and sing
La-la-la-la, let's have fun dancing
Ring-a, ring-a, ring-a
Ring-a, ring-a-ring
We will go hand in hand
And have fun jumping around
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song