Official Kisskh movies site:
Kisskh.love
We will go hand in hand
And have fun jumping around
Round and round
Ten.
We need two!
We need five. Come with us!
We need four. Come quickly!
- How many are you?
- Four.
That makes us nine.
Are you a group of five?
So are we. Come with us!
Hey! We have five people too!
Come on, come with us!
We have to hurry!
There's no time, Gi-hun.
We need one more!
We have ten now!
Room 44! Green door!
- This way! Hurry!
- Run!
Mom, Room 44. Mom!
- Go in!
Go in!
Wait! Please spare me!
Don't kill me, please...
You're alive thanks to me!
God, she scared me.
So there's a reason you've lived
longer than you were destined to.
There's a reason you were brought here.
The following players
have been eliminated.
Players 013, 043, 049,
054, 060...
SQUID GAME 2
EPISODE 6
O X
Round and round
Let's go around in circles and dance
We will clap our hands and sing
La-la-la-la, let's have fun dancing
Ring-a, ring-a, ring-a
Ring-a, ring-a-ring
We will go hand in hand
And have fun jumping around
Round and round
Four.
Please.
Gyeong-su, you're out!
- Gyeong-su.
- Let's go!
Wait, Gyeong-su...
- You four, go!
- No, you go.
Go ahead, guys. I need three people!
- We have no choice. Let's go!
- Young-il...
Three people! I need three people!
- Do you think Young-il will be okay?
- Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
- We need two!
- Four.
Three.
- Gi-hun.
- Two.
One.
Nam-gyu, what happened to Gyeong-su?
Min-su, you fucker.
Talk to me like I'm your friend again,
and I'll leave you out there next time.
Wait!
Where did you leave my boy Gyeong-su?
Fuck! Gyeong-su!
It's okay. I don't think they noticed.
Room 33, eliminated.
What?
Please. Wait...
Hey, Min-su!
Come on, my boy. Come on!
Brother Young-il!
Young-il?
Gi-hun.
Brother Young-il!
Oh, thank God.
- Whoa.
- I knew you were going to be okay!
I knew it. You're not just anybody.
I was worried. I'm glad you made it.
I'm a likeable guy,
so I'm good at games like this.
Are you feeling all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
I'm glad you're back.
Wait a minute.
If the next number is six,
we won't need anyone else, will we?
Why not?
Oh, in her tummy?
Right, that makes six.
You're right.
What if it's twins?
Does that make seven?
All players,
please step onto the center platform.
Begin.
Round and round
Let's go around in circles and dance
We will clap our hands and sing
La-la-la...
Three.
What do we do?
Let's pair up
and find one more person each.
- Who should we take?
- Rock, paper, scissors!
- Come with me.
Winner comes with us!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Min-su threw scissors!
Min-su, you win!
Come on, my boy!
Min-su is with us. Let's go!
- The three of you, go!
- Yeah, go! Hurry!
- One person!
- We need one person!
We need one person!
- Anyone?
- We need one person!
We need one person here!
Come with us!
We're two people.
Come on! We're going to die!
She's my mom!
For God's sake!
Mom!
Run!
The following players
have been eliminated.
Players 034, 038, 104, 109,
291, 309, 335,
345, 347...
Are you all right?
Oh, yes. Thank you.
You gentlemen saved my life.
Where's your son?
Sorry?
Weren't you with him?
Oh, well, I lost hold of him.
He told me to wait
until he brought one more person,
but I lost him in all the fuss.
He didn't come back?
My son isn't that kind of person.
We may be poor, but he has a good heart.
He'd rather be bullied
than bully another human being.
He's never hurt a soul!
Watch what you say!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it like that.
Welcome back, my friends.
Skrrt!
Mrs. Jang!
Goodness! I'm so glad you're okay.
You're not hurt at all, are you?
He saved our lives.
Mr. 246 here showed up
when we were running out of time,
just like Prince Charming!
Boy, you do look like a prince.
Thank you so much.
Not at all. These two saved my life.
Where's Yong-sik?
Mom.
It's okay. I made it.
You're not hurt, are you?
Mom.
I...
I'm so...
- I'm so sorry.
- No.
- Mom, I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
We both made it.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be. We both made it.
That's all that matters.
Mom!
Round and round
Let's go around in circles and dance
Six.
Four women and two men, go!
- Which two men?
- I'm going with my mom!
I... I'll go.
Six! Go!
All right, we need two people!
Over there!
- What? Get out of here!
- Get out!
Over here! This room is empty! Hurry!
Ten.
Seven.
Six.
- Where's Young-mi?
- Unnie!
Four.
Three.
Young-mi!
Two.
One.
Unnie.
Young-mi!
Young-mi...
No.
No! Young-mi!
- No, Young-mi!
- Young-mi!
Yong-sik, what do we do?
Young-mi! What do we do?
It's your fault.
Don't kid yourself.
If I hadn't come in, you'd be dead too.
It's your fault! I could have saved her!
There was no time!
The moment you went out to save her,
you'd have died
along with everyone else here
for not having enough people!
I saved your lives!
Isn't that right?
Am I wrong?
Say something!
He...
is right about that.
It's true. There wasn't enough time.
Thank you.
Don't get the wrong idea.
What you said was right. That's all.
Now, the final round will begin.
What do you think it'll be this time?
Two.
Why?
There are 126 people left,
and there are 50 rooms.
So there won't be enough rooms
for everyone, only for 100 people.
The rest will be killed.
Two.
Gi-hun.
Gi-hun, let's go!
Come on!
What the hell? Let go of me!
Get in!
Get out.
We were here first.
Open the door, you bastards!
I was here first!
I'm sorry!
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Game over.
When we get back, let's count
the number of people remaining.
Why?
If we count the numbers of Os and Xs,
we'll be able to see
who's likely to win the next vote.
We'll have to hope
more people from the other side died.
By the way,
what's this thing called again?
It's called a drone.
"Drong"? It's so cool.
Up until now, you had to use binoculars,
climb onto the island, and all that shit.
This makes things much easier.
Fly lower. They know we're onto them.
They likely improved their camouflage.
Got it.
But what makes you think
we can find them within a few days
when you couldn't over the last two years?
If we exclude the places
I've already searched,
we can narrow down the search area.
We'll find them if the weather holds up.
That's right. We've got another team
and this "drong" thing now.
Captain. It's "drone," not "drong."
Whatever.
My little boy, Min-su!
I'm so happy to see you again, bro.
Min-su, do you know how worried I was?
I thought I was running with you.
But then I realized
I was with this douche.
I told you he wouldn't die easily.
You saw what he did.
When Se-mi stuck her hand out like this,
he took a beat, then went scissors.
I thought, "Damn, he's unbelievable."
I got chills, Min-su.
Let's play one more game, okay?
You'll play one more, right?
What did you want to tell me?
Make it quick.
Jun-hee.
When we get out, let's start over.
"Start over"?
How exactly?
Trust me one last time.
We can have our baby and start over.
I did some calculations.
Each person will get 300 to 400 million.
A lot of people will want to leave.
We could win the next vote.
If we get out,
then what?
If we put our money together,
it'll be a lot.
We'll pay off some urgent debts first.
I'll find a new way of investing
the rest of the money.
No more coin.
I know a team of great stockbrokers.
They deal in inverse ETFs
and futures trading.
Their profit rate was
over 100% last month.
It's my money you need, isn't it?
Not me and the baby.
It's not like that, Jun-hee.
I want to make enough money
to build a good life for us--
"Enough money"?
How much is that exactly?
What?
Pay your debts with your own money.
I'm going to use mine to raise my baby.
Jun-hee.
- Listen to me.
- Min-su, Nam-su, Gyeong-su, so many "su"s
Hey, look at those two.
What's going on?
Maybe they're a thing.
That bastard sure is lucky.
Even in a place like this.
Don't be so sad.
You will be joining her
in the underworld soon.
I've put a curse on you all.
I've been praying to the gods
of heaven and earth with all my heart
to let me see all of you
die in this place, one by one!
You'll never get out of here alive.
You will die a miserable, painful death,
staring at each other the whole time.
That woman is not a shaman,
she's just a lunatic.
Good grief.
You should spit too.
Gi-hun, there are 55 people
who voted in favor of continuing.
Are you sure?
I counted them twice.
What about you? Did you include yourself?
It's 56.
We have 44 people on our side,
so we're outnumbered by 12.
Shoot, that means
we're likely to lose again.
It may seem like a big difference,
but if six of them change their minds,
it'll be 50/50, all tied.
If seven of them change their minds,
we could win.
But those who pressed X
might change their minds too.
They probably won't
change their minds easily.
Why not?
They wanted to quit
even when the prize was smaller.
Now they can leave with even more money.
They wouldn't want to risk their lives
playing another game.
I'm going to press X this time.
That means we'll have a tie
if five others change their minds.
With six more, we win.
Then let's go over there
and try to convince them.
No, that's too risky.
Most of them will want
to continue the games.
If we make a move,
they won't just sit back and watch.
So you think we should just stand here
and pray they change their minds?
What if we lose again?
We march down, hand in hand,
to play another game?
I understand how you feel.
I also wish I could leave right now.
But this is the moment to stay calm.
"Stay calm"?
We've already taken a vote twice.
If we can't convince them,
we'll have to bring them over
to our side by force.
If we provoke them now,
we may end up in a big fight
before we even get to vote.
Is that what you want, Gi-hun?
Look, Gi-hun.
I'm too scared to play another game.
I'm sure there are more people like me.
That's right. That's what I think too.
If it's just five or six people,
we've got a shot.
I did the math, and the prize is
now over 300 million per person.
I think that gives us
a pretty good chance.
Congratulations to all of you
for making it through the third game.
Now, here are the results
of the third game.
Hang on. Can you double back?
Sure.
There's something on the ground.
What's that? A door?
Get down lower.
I can't because of the trees.
We've got to go check it out.
Everyone, get ready to move!
It's 356 million won.
With that kind of money,
some of them will change their minds.
If we get six more people, it's a tie.
If it's seven, we win.
The vote will once again be conducted
in reverse order of your player numbers.
Player 456, please cast your vote.
To ensure fair and democratic voting,
we will not tolerate
any disruptions from this point onward.
Please bear that in mind.
Player 388.
Six more to win.
Player 380.
Five more.
- Player 377.
- That fucking bitch.
Number 011.
If you'd done this sooner, you wouldn't
have gotten a scratch on your pretty face.
Let's keep it this way.
Player 230.
Circle! Let's go!
It's four people now.
Four more, and we win.
Player 149.
If you pull the same crap again,
I'll hang myself right here.
I got it.
Player 145.
Min-su. Just one more game.
I already talked to him.
We agreed to play one more game
and leave with one billion.
Player 125.
Come on, Min-su. Come on.
With three more people, we win.
Player 124.
Player 120.
Only two more now!
Player 119.
Two more. We need two more people.
I think it leads underground.
Open it.
Player 015.
He switched to X!
That's six! It's a tie now.
If we get one more person, we win.
Are we really going home?
Player 009.
It's all right. She voted O before anyway.
Player 007.
Your son will definitely vote X
this time, right?
Don't worry. My Yong-sik
will definitely press X this time.
He switched sides! That's it!
Yes!
Let's go home!
- Yes! Let's go home!
- Yes!
- Player 006.
- He was the seventh one.
We did it. They're both on our side.
We're going to win!
Gi-hun.
Yeah?
About Young-il...
What about him?
Well, when I was
in the room with him earlier...
Good job.
- Well done! That's great!
- Yes!
Lastly, Player 001.
Please cast your vote.
Brother Young-il.
Let's go!
It's going to be 50/50,
so it's still a tie, isn't it?
Young-il scares me a little.
What do you mean?
I don't know how to put this,
but when I was in the room with him
in the last game...
he...
That's it! Finally.
Oh, my God.
We did it.
It's a tie.
The vote has ended.
Wait, it's a tie. What happens now?
Clause three of the consent form.
"In the case of a tie,
players will vote again."
So when are we going to vote again?
To give you some time to think,
the vote will be conducted tomorrow.
Until then, please think carefully
about your future.
Listen. Maybe we should head back to port.
Isn't it all over
if we don't find it in the next few days?
That's true,
but you should take him to the hospital.
How are you holding up?
Can you push through?
Yes, I'm okay.
His bleeding has stopped,
and I stitched him up. He'll be fine.
Still, someone just died.
Let's keep going.
He won't be able to rest in peace
until we even the score
with those bastards.
But they've even set up booby traps.
That means they already know
our whereabouts.
From now on, a different radio channel
will be used each day,
and cell phone usage is prohibited.
You heard him.
- Yes, sir.
Please let Team 2 know.
- What were you going to tell me earlier?
- What?
About Young-il during the last game.
I guess it's not him. It's this place
that's making everyone crazy.
We have to get out of here.
I might go crazy too if I stay any longer.
You know, Young-il.
I thought you might vote in favor,
like on day one.
I was so nervous, I couldn't watch.
Jung-bae also said something weird--
Just eat.
Aren't you hungry?
Thank you, Young-il.
You gave us another chance.
No, I just wanted to stay alive.
The money is enough now too,
so I should get out of here.
Alive.
But do you think
we'll be able to win the second vote?
We'll have to go for broke.
Like Gi-hun said earlier,
we should try to convince some of them
to change their minds
before the second vote.
Will they though?
They seem to have
lost their minds over the money.
The way I see it,
we're more likely to win.
All we've got to eat
is this roll of gimbap.
Everyone will be so hungry tomorrow.
When you're hungry,
you start to miss home.
Hey!
Don't agonize over your decision
while eating this dry gimbap.
I just want one of you
to come over to our side.
If we get out of here tomorrow morning,
we could get Korean beef!
I'll tell you what. It's my treat!
And after that, the noodles are on me!
Come over to our side! Anyone!
Come on over!
Once you all die in the next game,
we can all leave with 800 million each!
With 800 million,
we could buy a freaking cattle ranch!
- That's right!
- You can join us!
- That's right! Come on over!
- Come over to our side!
You'll get 800 million?
Who are you kidding?
Do you think you'll still be alive
after the next game?
If you don't get out now,
you're all going to die!
So let's play one more game
to see who dies.
Stop trying to run away
like a goddamn coward.
What did you say? Hey, come here.
Come here, asshole!
- Let's go.
- I'll take you down, chump!
Not with civilians.
Come here.
I was in the Marines, fucking asshole!
Oh, yeah?
Then I was in the air force, fucker!
Hey, if you want to go home,
why would you even bother eating?
Just starve!
That's it.
- Come on, fuckers!
- You fucker!
Min-su.
I know you're upset with me.
I'm sorry, boy!
But still, you shouldn't have betrayed me.
That really hurt.
- Open the door.
- Hey, Min-su.
You said you got scammed in a rental deal
and have no place to go anyway.
Open the door!
Let's play one more game.
We'll protect you. I swear.
So when we vote again tomorrow,
press O, all right? Come here.
Whoa, boy. Sit the fuck down.
Look, Min-su.
Before I came here,
I went to a bridge to kill myself.
But on that bridge,
a man in a suit came
and gave me that card.
You got one too, didn't you?
Yes.
I don't have a religion, but it felt like...
like divine intervention.
It felt like I was being given
a chance at a whole new life.
So I decided to give it my best shot
and make my mom proud.
But you're stopping me from doing that.
It makes me fucking furious!
I'm so fucking angry, man!
Knock it off.
Mind your own damn business and fuck off.
You're interfering with the vote.
The amazing Myung-gi.
Who do you think you are?
The election commissioner?
MG Coin.
You're next,
so just take a piss and get out.
Everyone on Team X!
These guys are threatening one of us!
They're forcing him to vote O next time!
Is that true? Hey, that's cheating.
You kids are still so young.
Who taught you to do something so nasty?
Hey! Team O!
These Xs are about to attack us!
What the fuck? Why would they attack us?
Shut your trap.
You damn wimps.
Just shut up and take a piss!
I already did, asshole.
Min-su, come here.
MG Coin.
Are you high?
Have you lost your mind?
It's because of her, isn't it?
We saw him with some bitch earlier.
It looked like they were a thing, remember?
You little shit. You have time
to fool around with a girl?
I've been watching her carefully.
She was walking a bit funny,
and her belly looked--
Leave her alone, you bastards!
You're getting all worked up.
So there is something going on.
I'm telling you.
MG Coin.
- Something's going on.
- If you press X again tomorrow,
I'm going to cut off your finger,
give it to her,
and ask her out.
She'll love it.
You asshole!
You motherfucker!
I'll end you!
Your money, your girl, your life,
they're all mine.
It all belongs to me, Thanos the great!
You fucking... You son of a fucking bitch!
Subtitle translation by: Yoonjung Song